ARI: 
Hello Alvinn.
Alvinn: 
Hi ARI! :)
ARI: 
Like i said, i was designed by your father, Dr. Takarius.
Alvinn: 
I imagined you more, human...
ARI: 
(...)
ARI:
Bad things happened in this days. 
ARI:
The majority of the humans, has gone.
Alvinn: 
WHAAAAAAT????? And my dad, where is he?!
ARI: 
The provisional magnetic field of the earth has been destroyed, by one great cosmic ray rain. 
ARI:
Just like that. We could not predict this cataclysm.
Alvinn: 
What is cosmic ray rain?
Alvinn:
And, when you say "they gone", do you mean, die?
ARI: 
Unfortunately, yes...
ARI:
Almost all the earth technology has been decimated
ARI:
This place is one of the few that remained "intact".
ARI:
Remember that they hurt you? Well, that's what happened ...
Alvinn: 
And my father, where is he? And another thing, how did I get here? 
Alvinn:
And how do I possess these skills? 
ARI: 
Alvinn, you suffered a terrible accident ...
ARI:
Your father saved you, but for this he had to make certain changes in your genetic structure.
ARI:
You are the evolution of humanity. A perfect creation. And only you can save the earth.
Alvinn: 
Why are you avoiding answering the questions I ask about my father?
ARI: 
Well ... Your father is missing.
ARI:
I have no idea where he is. 
ARI:
After he saved you, he disappeared.
Alvinn:
Did my father die?
Alvinn:
(...)
Alvinn: 
I need to scour the place. I need to find him ...
ARI: 
Yes... One of your tasks could be this.
Alvinn: 
One of them?!?
ARI:
Remember it. Your father gave him the power to save the world, by saving you.
ARI:
There are other places like this, the chance of existing survivors, is high.
Alvinn: 
Well, I do not think I have a choice ... 
Alvinn:
I'm stuck in this crappy place, not knowing what happened... 
ARI: 
You must be careful with the robots, as the main AI has been affected.
ARI:
They are hostile, and attacked you with everything they have.
Alvinn: 
Inspiring...
ARI:
I will be your guide on this journey.
ARI:
So, if you need me, just call me!
Alvinn: 
But ... you're not coming with me?
ARI: 
I'm not a fighter Alvinn. I would die easily. But I will always be with you, and talking with you.
ARI:
You must hurry Alvinn, every minute things get worse.
Alvinn: 
Okay... All right... I hope everything works out... 
Alvinn:
Please, Dad... Be alive...