Alvinn:
Ouch! This things burn my skin... What is this energy balls...
Alvinn:
ARI, are you there?
ARI: 
They are particles.
Alvinn: 
They hurt me...
Alvinn:
But... although the pain, i fell like this things energize me, and this is pretty wierd.
ARI: 
Well, you must have safe, if you get hitted by many particles, you will die…
Alvinn: 
Morrer?!!!
ARI: 
You have a unique skill. 
ARI:
You can generate a force field around you. No human can see the particles, just you, you can see their trail.
ARI:
This force field will make the particles do not hurt you anymore.
ARI:
The field absorb the energy of this particles to you. 
ARI:
In addition, you can use an energy absorbed for several things.
ARI:
A amazing skill!
Alvinn:
What?!?
Alvinn:
I dont believe in you...
Alvinn: 
How i active this... power?
ARI: 
Focus, is something that already born with you. 
ARI: 
One thing, to activate this field, energy is necessary.
ARI:
Another thing, how did you realize, if the field is deactivated, the particles will hurt you, but still, they will give energy for you.
ARI:
Well, be careful, see you soon.
Alvinn:
No, wait!!
ARI:
(...)
Alvinn: 
Okay... 
Alvinn:
I do not have anything to lose.... 
Alvinn:
Let me try!