ARI: 
Hello Alvinn...
Alvinn: 
Who is talking?
ARI: 
I am ARI.
ARI:
An artificial intelligence, designed to create others artificial intelligences.
Alvinn: 
Awesome!!!
Alvinn:
My father has already told me about one of this projects, who is similar to you.
ARI: 
Yout father designed me.
Alvinn: 
Hahahah... My daddy rocks!! 
Alvinn:
Where is he? 
Alvinn:
And... well... why am i here? 
Alvinn:
In fact... how did I get here?
ARI: 
Come to me, and i will explain this better. Just walk forward, always ...
ARI:
Ah, cuidado para não cair nos buracos!
Alvinn: 
Buracos? '-'
Alvinn:
ARI?
ARI:
(...)
Alvinn: 
ARI?!?
ARI:
(...)
Alvinn:
What a weird stuff...